Scarlett S. Verheul

I am a lifelong programmer and tech enthusiast with over 12 years of industry experience, primarily in development roles focused on Hosting, SaaS, ATS, and Platform Integration projects. I believe in using the right tool for the job, with a particular emphasis on backend development, server automatic provisioning, and hardware/OS integration.

Personal Information

Location: Capelle aan den IJssel / Randstad / Netherlands (*CEST* +2)

Citizenship: Nederlands **Date Of Birth**: 14-02-1994

Email: scarlett.verheul@gmail.com

Github: <u>ScarlettSamantha</u> **LinkedIn**: <u>ScarlettVerheul</u>

Key: https://scarlettbytes.nl/gpg

Employment Type:

Full Time | Remote/Hybrid

EXPERIENCE

I3D.net, Capelle aan den IJssel — *Infrastructure Software* Engineer

Sept 2021 - PRESENT

Domain: Hosting, Network Automatisation, Networking, PHP7→8, Python, Laravel At I3D I worked on maintaining and improving/rebuilding various production systems focusing on server infrastructure and automated server provisioning/network automation and processing raw data gathered from telemetry into a workable application.

I also worked on the D&I team to improve equity and access to every employee.

Digivotion B.V., Rotterdam — Tech Lead

Feb 2019 - Sep 2021

Domain: SaaS, Devops, PHP5→7, Code Rework, Modernization, Zend 1, Server Management, Laravel, Python3, Microservices, Project Management

At Digivotion I worked on improving and developing parts of the SAAS systems offered to customers, I worked on the backend and filled a day to day technical leadership role. I also worked on improving the developer experience by migrating away from aging infrastructure to newer systems.

Supportdesk B.V., Rotterdam — Software Engineer | Development/Incidents-CERT

Aug 2016 - Feb 2019

Domain: Development-AAS, Webplatform (E-Commerce), CERT, Magento1, PHP5 My time at supportdesk mostly focused on implementing direct (semi-)custom wishes of customers into their web applications. I also worked on the CERT/Security incidents teams for when a customer had an security incident/hack on a server. I also worked on improving the performance and scaling from customers on their platforms.

SKILLS (1 ... 5)

PHP5/7/8(5),
Python3(4), Git (4),
Linux-Debish-Cent(3), Bash(3),
Laravel/Eloquent(3), CI/CD(3),
Pipelines(3), MySQL (3), Networking (3),
Microservice (3), Docker(3), Flask(3),
Rabbitmq (3), Nginx (3), Apache (3)
K8's(2), Micropython(2), PostgreSQL(2),
Django(2), PL/Python(2), C# (2),
Pure/jQuery Javascript (2), NumPy (2),
Hardware development(2),
Game Dev(1)

Other Skills (/Buzzwords):

Rest(full) - Scrum/Agile - Waterfall - Multithreading (Python, Not PHP) - Elasticsearch - Jira/Atlassian(2) -Performance Optimisation - BMC -(para)Virtualisation - Github/Gitlab - SNMP - (py/php)Unit Test/PyTest - OOP - Xdebug - DDD - Netbox -RS232 - Cacti - Documentation -DHCP - IP - Networking - TCP/IP Suite - SAAS - Swagger - OpenApi -I18N - Ubiquiti - DNS - JSON -Composer - Psr[1...18] - Juniper Api - SDI12 - LibreNMS - DDD - XML -Markdown - Logging - Sentry -Project - (protocol) SPI - KVM management - Peer review - D&I Computer/Server - Internal Hardware - LDAP - Redfish

Helloprint, Drukzo, Rotterdam — Team Lead IT

July 2015 - Aug 2016

Domain: Startup, Quick Iteration, PHP5, External API's, Custom ecommerce services

Here I worked on Improving the internal and external platform and implementing new systems. I also worked on creating a team to share the workload and facilitate that. I also worked on integrating various external API's

[Skipped 2 experiences (available on linkedin)]

Drecomm B.V, Rotterdam — PHP Developer

Sept 2012 - Aug 2014

Domain: Project Development, PHP5, B2B, Typo3, Drupal, Frameworkless

I worked on improving customers' applications with new features or bug fixes or installations. I also worked with different teams to help out when extra developers were needed.

Here I started to specialize more into the server/backend parts of the job. [Skipped 1 experiences (available on linkedin)]

PROJECTS(ABSTRACT) / AREAS OF WORK

Linux/Network -

Having used linux as my primary Os for years now I am very comfortable in the unix env and am used to working with servers remote or locally via cli or programmatically. And am a believer in the (FL)-OSS movement.

PHP Development -

I have worked on various projects ranging from saas to internal company needs. This was most of the time combined with updating/improving existing production code bases. I worked here with diverse frameworks mostly Laravel/Eloquent(>4) and a bit Symfony and Zend(1) over the years

Python Development -

Python has been my goto language when working on projects where more performance was needed (due to php not having threading, at least till v8) and/or more os integration. It's my personal favorite language and most of my private projects are written in it. I prefer pure python with libs and objects from things that I need and for more complex projects flask/django

Workflow/Style -

I prefer to operate in a waterfall, scrum, or agile environment, utilizing a task/ticket management tool within a git-based workflow on a remote git server. My ideal setup involves a robust D(/O)TAP process with pipelines to manage development and versioning. I favor the Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) paradigm for most projects and prefer strict/hard typing over inferred typing. I believe in maintaining simplicity over unnecessary complexity to ensure observability and performance.

EDUCATION

Grafisch Lyceum, Rotterdam — Application/Web Developer

Aug 2010 - Feb 2012 (Finished in 1.5 years instead of normal 4)

I followed the application developer post secondary program, I received my degree in a hastened way due to finishing all the degree work early.

HOBBIES/INTERESTS

Traveling, MicroElectronics, Music, HPC, Programming, AI, Pets, Technology, Foreign Relations, Global Politics, Current Affairs, Space, Airsoft, 3D Printing, Warhammer 40K, Gaming(4x, Strategy)

LANGUAGES

REFERENCES

Available upon request please contact me.

NOTES

I choose to work only directly with companies or projects without recruiting agencies or complex middlemen.

I am open to both salaried positions and contractor (ZZP) roles, depending on the project and location and compensation.

This C.V. was handmade and as I am *dyslexic* it might contain spelling mistakes/errors.

If this C.V. was given to you by an external recruiter/recruiting agency, then this c.v has been harvested without my consent or approval.

SECURITY

This document has been <u>signed</u>(.sig file) with my <u>GPG key</u>. If it is not signed or a bad signature message is given upon verification, then this document has been modified without my permission.

Signing Key Fingerprint(s):
RSA4096[pub] 2F98 5406 3563
1EEC A083 5196 744D 7EC1 5F90